export const deckData = {
    'Quote': {
        title: 'Quote',
        questions: [
            {
                question: 'Who is the author of "It is a far, far better thing that I do, than I have ever done; it is a far, far better rest that I go to than I have ever known."',
                answer: 'Charles Dickens',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who is the author of "The secret of getting ahead is getting started."',
                answer: 'Mark Twain',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who is the author of "There is nothing noble in being superior to your fellow man; true nobility is being superior to your former self."',
                answer: 'Ernest Hemingway',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who is the author of "We loved with a love that was more than love."',
                answer: 'Edgar Allan Poe',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who is the author of "Ask not what your country can do for you â€” ask what you can do for your country."',
                answer: 'John F. Kennedy',
            }
        ]
    },
    'Inventor': {
        title: 'Inventor',
        questions: [
            {
                question: 'Who invented radio communication?',
                answer: 'Guglielmo Marconi',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who invented plastic bags?',
                answer: 'Sten Gustaf Thulin',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who discovered electricity?',
                answer: 'Benjamin Franklin',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who first invented the "first" light bulb?',
                answer: 'Thomas Edison',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who first airplanes?',
                answer: 'The Wright brothers',
            },
            {
                question: 'Who is known for the theory of E=MC2?',
                answer: 'Albert Einstein',
            }
        ]
    }
}